http://www.treehelp.com/privacy-policy/

Good Directions
Droll Yankees, Inc.
TreeHelp Annual Care Kits
Care for your own trees with our 3-step do-it-yourself maintenance kit.
Privacy Policy
TreeHelp.com, Inc. (TreeHelp) is committed to providing you the opportunity for a positive experience during your visit to our web site, while respecting and striving to protect your on-line privacy. Because protecting your privacy is very important, we have adopted this policy to safeguard your personal information and protect its confidentiality. We will limit the collection and use of personal information to what is necessary to administer our business, provide you with the highest quality visit, and offer you information we think will be of interest. We will not disclose any individual information to other organizations unless we provide you with advance notice and choice.
Collection of Voluntary Information
TreeHelp collects personal information from our visitors on a voluntary basis. Personal information may include name, title, address, phone number, e-mail address, etc. The individual information we collect is used to facilitate the on-line experience through enhanced navigation or to suggest areas in which we may improve the structure and content of the site.  In the future, this information may be used as a means to communicate informational and promotional information from TreeHelp, but you will have the option to opt out of all such communication.
Information Collected during the Order Process
TreeHelp also collects mandatory information from users wishing to make a purchase.  This information includes name, billing and shipping address, phone number, and e-mail address.  This information is used to contact you with order-related communication (such as an electronic invoice).  An account is also created for you with the goal of making future orders more convenient.  You can view your account information by clicking on the "My Account" link at the top of the page.
If you choose to pay for your order via our Secure Online Credit Card payment server, you will be required to submit financial information such as credit card number and expiration date.  This information is used for the sole purpose of completing the transaction.  TreeHelp.com, Inc. does notpermanently store this information.
Collection of Aggregate Information
Our web server tracks and collects general information about your visit to our website. We collect these statistics to determine the number of daily visitors to our site, the daily requests for particular files, the types of browsers our visitors use, the visitors' domain names, and countries of origin.
TreeHelp employs "cookie" technology to help visitors move faster through certain areas of the site. When you sign on to our site, we pass a cookie to your computer. A cookie is a string of information that's sent by a Web site and stored on the hard drive or temporarily in your computer's memory. This leads to quicker navigation and a generally more positive experience searching for the information you desire.
All personal information you provide to TreeHelp is secured on our server with restricted access. We reserve the right to use agents, who are bound by strict confidentiality guidelines, to perform storage and processing functions. Only designated employees or agents who need to carry out legitimate business functions are permitted to view your personal data. Employees or agents who violate this privacy policy are subject to disciplinary actions, up to and including termination.
Outside Links
To facilitate navigation, this site may contain links to other sites. We will make every effort to link only to sites that share our high standards and respect for privacy. However, we are not responsible for the content or the privacy practices employed by organizations sponsoring these other sites.
We reserve the right to change this policy at any time by notifying visitors of the existence of the new privacy policy.
×
OK
Join our newsletter
Sign up for our newsletter to receive special offers and promotions
Email Address
free shipping on orders over $100
Canada: 416-491-1436
Where To Find Us:
